https://www.mutoh.eu/en-us/privacy.aspx

Cookies help us collect information about how you use our website but we do not store personally identifiable information about you in our cookies data. We use cookies to make your visits on our websites efficient. By clicking 'I accept' or continuing to use our website, you agree to our use of cookies.
I accept
Quick cookies verification
More cookies information
Strictly necessary cookies
Language cookie
Marketing cookies
Facebook Pixel
Performance cookies
Privacy Policy
Privacy DeclarationMutoh Europe NV is aware that the privacy of its customers and the protection of their data are important.This privacy declaration describes what measures we take to ensure the protection of personal data in accordance with Belgian privacy legislation and the European General Data Protection Regulation (AVG – GDPR).Application areaMutoh Europe NV manages this website and is responsible for the processing of the personal data in the various processes and systems that are applicable or in use at our company.The purpose of this policy is to indicate which personal data we collect and how we use your data after you have visited our website.Which data is collected?We do not need your personal data for the major part of our website. Your personal data will only be processed if it is done lawfully. We will only do so if it is necessary for one of the following reasons:for the implementation of a contractif required by lawbecause it is of vital importancefor the public interestfor a legitimate interestMutoh Europe NV may collect and process the following categories of personal data:Name, titleAddressContact informationCompany We can also ask you for additional/optional information when:You are filling out forms on our websiteWhen we contact you personally (chat, phone, e-mail, trade fairs or events) In addition, we can also collect and process information via our website or the devices you use. It can involve:Location data collected via social media or the IP-address of your deviceInformation about the web pages you visit, your IP-address, browser type, access time and operating system This information is aggregated and is not used to identify you.Mutoh Europe NV may also collect publicly accessible information to verify the information we have collected and to manage and expand our activities.Why do we collect your data?Mutoh Europe NV collects the above information to get an idea of your needs and to offer you a better service, more specifically for the following purposes:To give information about our products and servicesTo respond to your (online) questions regarding our products and servicesTo periodically send e-mails about products and services, special offers, seminars and knowledge eventsTo contact you for market researchService to your company and employeesHow do we collect your data?We do this in various ways, including:Personal contact/telephone/e-mail/chatContact forms via our websiteContacts at seminars, fairs and networking eventsTransfer to third partiesWithin our standard business activities, the data we collect can be exchanged with other subsidiaries of Mutoh Europe NV and with our distribution partners. This always happens within a contractual cooperation in accordance with the GDPR legislation.We never sell or rent personal information to other people or companies. If we use an external processor contractually connected to Mutoh Europe NV, we will always ensure that your data is treated confidentially and secure. It is not allowed for external processors to use your personal data on their own initiative.Minimum data processingThe personal information we collect is adequate and relevant to our purposes. We restrict the collection of your personal data to a minimum, necessary for the purpose for which we process the data.What are your rights and how can you exercise them?People from whom personal data is collected have several rights. These are listed in the GDPR legislation and include:Right to access, change and delete dataRight to data transferRight of objectionRight to limit the processingGDPR - Chapter III - Rights of the person concerned These rights can be exercised free of charge by submitting a clear request to our administration. It states the right to which you wish to appeal with explanations and how we can contact you. You can submit the request via the following e-mail address: privacy@mutoh.euContact informationAll data are included in files of Mutoh Europe NV. As controller, we are responsible for compliance with our data protection policy at all our locations.Mutoh Europe NVArchimedesstraat 13B-8400 OostendeTel: +32 59 561400E-mail:privacy@mutoh.euMutoh Europe NV follows all regulations imposed by the Belgian Privacy Commission. If you do not agree with the way in which we process your data, you can contact the commission.Drukpersstraat 35, 1000 BrusselTel+32 (0)2 274 48 00 - Fax +32 (0)2 274 48 35commission@privacycommission.be https://www.privacycommission.be/nl/contact  Policy changesMutoh Europe NV will periodically update this policy to ensure that its reflects the way we process your personal data at a given time. The updated version of this policy will take immediately effect upon publication. Please check this page regularly to ensure that you are always aware on how we collect and process your data.
Need help? Contact us!
)
